{
    "subject": "resource/University_of_the_East",
    "predicate": "property/established",
    "object": "1946",
    "human_readable": "The University of the East was established in 1946.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8778690695762634,
            "question": "When was the University of the East founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7219313979148865,
            "question": "In what decade was the University of the East established?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5128008127212524,
            "question": "What year did the University of the East begin operations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5115668773651123,
            "question": "What kind of institution is the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45008090138435364,
            "question": "Can you tell me something about the history of the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4195229411125183,
            "question": "Is the University of the East a relatively new institution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3230365216732025,
            "question": "What significant event happened in the year 1946 related to education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28860142827033997,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from the University of the East?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2713935375213623,
            "question": "How old is the University of the East currently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2172645777463913,
            "question": "What might be some challenges facing the University of the East today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The University of the East was established in 1946.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6993_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old is the University of the East currently?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6993_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable alumni from the University of the East?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6993_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant event happened in the year 1946 related to education?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6993_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6993_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents explicitly state that \"The history of the University of the East starts in September 1946\" and \"The University of the East (UE) is a private university in Manila, Philippines. UE was founded in 1946 as the Philippine College of Commerce and Business Administration (PCCBA)\". This information supports the statement that The University of the East was established in 1946."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}